let questionwrs = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "I need to work hard so ___ I can pass the exam.",
        answer: "that",
        options: [
            "that",
            "so",
            "but",
            "since",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "___ he was the best candidate, he didn't win the elections.",
        answer: "Although",
        options: [
            "And",
            "But",
            "Where",
            "Although",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "___ you come back from your trip, we'll meet to discuss the problem.",
        answer: "when",
        options: [
            "So",
            "where",
            "when",
            "And",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "They said that the movie was fantastic, ___ I watched it.",
        answer: "so",
        options: [
            "so",
            "and",
            "that",
            "or",
        ]
    },{
        numb: 5,
        question: "___ he was very ill, he didn't take any medicine.",
        answer: "Although",
        options: [
            "And",
            "But",
            "Where",
            "Although",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "I don't know ___ I can buy a pair of jeans.",
        answer: "where",
        options: [
            "where",
            "and",
            "or",
            "so",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "She went to the shops ___ couldn't find anything that could fit her needs.",
        answer: "but",
        options: [
            "or",
            "but",
            "so",
            "since",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Everybody likes him because he is nice ___ helpful.",
        answer: "and",
        options: [
            "since",
            "although",
            "and",
            "so",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "___ he was angry with her, he didn't utter a word.",
        answer: "Since",
        options: [
            "Since",
            "Where",
            "But",
            "And",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Keep quiet __ go out.",
        answer: "or",
        options: [
            "and",
            "that",
            "or",
            "although",
        ]
    },
]